Guide to the Duke Ellington School of the Arts collection, 1966-2014 MS2329
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Duke Ellington School of the Arts collection
1966-2014
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2329
30.5 Linear Feet
The Duke Ellington School of the Arts was established in 1974 and remains the only D.C. public high school to offer a dual curriculum encompassing professional arts training and academic enrichment, in preparation for college and careers in the arts. This collection consists of material related to the Duke Ellington School of the Arts including scripts, syllabi, administrative files, correspondence, photographs, slides, audio, and video cassettes. It also includes material related to black theatre and other arts organizations; scripts, programs, flyers, articles, correspondence, and photographs. The collection dates from 1966-2014.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The Duke Ellington School of the Arts was established in 1974 and remains the only D.C. public high school to offer a dual curriculum encompassing professional arts training and academic enrichment, in preparation for college and careers in the arts.
By naming one of his jazz bands The Washingtonians, Duke Ellington made his home part of his persona. D.C. philanthropist and avid art collector Peggy Cooper Cafritz and the late dancer and choreographer Mike Malone returned the favor, building this school to house the creative soul of the District, and to reflect the rich cultural diversity of the United States. From the beginning, public and private partnerships have supported the school, which in 2000 evolved into the Duke Ellington School of the Arts Project (DESAP), which includes the D.C. Public Schools, the Ellington Fund, the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, and George Washington University.
Collection Scope and Content
The Duke Ellington School of the Arts collection consists of material related to the school, as well as pertaining to black theatre and other arts organizations. It includes administrative files, correspondence, scripts, syllabi, programs, flyers, articles, photographs, slides, audio and video cassettes. The collection dates from 1966-2014.
Collection Organization
Organized into 6 series: Facility rentals, The REP, Inc., Theatre material, Arts organizations, Duke Ellington School of the Arts, Audio and visual materials
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Duke Ellington School of the Arts, 25 September 2014 (2014.34)
Theater; Dance; Dance schools; Performing arts; Education; Duke Ellington School of the Arts
- Facility rentals, 1985-1989; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes administrative files related to the rental of facilities at the Duke Ellington School of the Arts. It also contains information about specific companies and groups that rented space. Dates covered include 1985-1989.
  - Administration, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Staff, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amerindia/Latin American Youth Center, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anacostia High School, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arts, D.C., 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ballet Center (The Chamber Ballet Ensemble), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beethoven Nightcappers, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cancellations, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Caribbean American Cultural Organization, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Charles Sumner School, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Charlin/Ellington Lecture Series, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Opera, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class International, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coca-Cola Mid-Atlantic Bottling Co. (Black History Essay Contest Awards), 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - College of Wooster, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Conferences/Workshops, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dar Al-Higrah (Islamic Assn. for Palestine), 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Rec, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Public Schools Summer Music Programs, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Youth Ensemble, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Deposits, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - District Curators, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dreamgirls, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Durrin Films, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ethiopian Theatre Ensemble, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown University, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown University - Billy Taylor, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hardy Middle School, 1987, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hexagon, Inc. (1/2), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hexagon, Inc. (2/2), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Horizons Theater, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - House Personnel, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - International Jazz Coalition, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Inti Illimani, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jean Pierre Jumez Concert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Kilimanjaro, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Levine School, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - McLean School of Ballet, 1966, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mid-Atlantic Coca-Cola Bottling Co., 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Miss D.C. Scholarship Pageant (1/2), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Miss D.C. Scholarship Pageant (2/2), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - National Dance Troupe, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - National Theater of the Performing Arts, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurement, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - New Playwright's Theatre, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - No Where Fast, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Office Equipment, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Phil's Photo, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Queen of the Blues, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rama Seminars, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ramzi el-Edlibi Dance Company, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rebecca Kelly Dance Company (1/2), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rebecca Kelly Dance Company (2/2), 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Rental Inquiries - General, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Theater Operations, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Washington Savoyards, Ltd. (1/2), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Washington Savoyards, Ltd. (2/2), 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sister's Circle, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Sokol, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stuart Gassner, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Summer Performing Arts Program for D.C. Public Schools, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Summer Jazz Program, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Teatro Pilipino, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Telescope Productions, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Theresa Kramer, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Toshi Reagon and Ritchie Havens, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Trade Route International, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - US/China Capital Cities Friendship Council, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - (User) Advisory Neighborhood Commission, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Video Team, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Washington Area Council on Alcoholism and Drug Abuse, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Washington Ballet, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Washington Male Chorale, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Washington Project for the Arts, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Whitman-Walker Clinic, n.d., undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - World Community Ascending Church, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Young Lawyers, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- The REP, Inc., 1972-1994; Series 2
  This series contains material from the organization The REP, Inc., a black oriented performing arts program in the Washington Community that was founded in November 1970. The REP provided professional training to aspriring artists and sought to expand the larger community's cultural enrichment and appreciation of black aesthetic. The series includes administrative files, resumes, correspondence, scripts, programs, flyers, and photographs. Dates covered include 1972-1994.
  - Advertising: Free Air Time (Television), 1983; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Community, 1978; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Art, 1978; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Arts D.C. Application (Programs and Correspondence), 1978-1982; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board Members, 1986; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, 1976-1984; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board Structure and Duties Of, 1984; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors - Carolyn Smith, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors - Intro, 1979-1982; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Bond Paper, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Business Transactions, 1980, 1986; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Company Member Contracts, 1980, 1984; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1992; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Commission of the Arts and Humanities, 1982; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Decades, 1974-1981; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation Reports, 1978; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Final Report FY-84, 1984; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Friends of The REP, Inc., 1981-1992; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising Reception, 1984; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gap Subscription and Useable Photos, 1973, 1980; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - General Organization Documents (1/2), 1988; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General Organization Documents (2/2), 1972-1984; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Generic Letter - Contract Form: Binding Groups and Organizations, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Generic Letter - Contribution "Thank You" Letter Form, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Generic Letter - Press Invitation, 1984; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Generic Letter - Thank You, 1983; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Generic Letter - Theatre Party, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1980-1986; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Grant and Labor Forms, 1986-1987; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Group Sales Packet (Original), 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - History of Organization (1/2), 1974-1976; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - History of Organization (2/2), 1978-1979; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Information (Productions): Work Request Order Form, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Information (Productions): Contracts - Blank, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - IRS Forms, 1983; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy Center, 1982; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Letterhead, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PSA Letter Head, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Letterhead - The REP, Inc., n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Loan Applications, 1982; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Loans - Riggs National Bank, 1977; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Loans - Riggs National Bank, 1979; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Loans - Riggs National Bank, 1980; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Loans - Riggs National Bank, 1983; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Mailing List, Board Members, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Mailing Lists: Maryland, Zip Codes Miscellaneous, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Mailing Lists: Virginia, Zip Codes Miscellaneous, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Codes 20001-20005, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Codes 20006-20008, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20009, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20010, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20011, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20012, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20016-20018
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Codes 20019-20020, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mailing Lists: Maryland, Zip Codes 20021-20023, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Code 20024, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mailing Lists: Maryland, Zip Code 20027, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mailing Lists: Wash., D.C., Zip Codes 20032-20037, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Mailing LIsts: Wash., D.C., Zip Codes 20059-on out, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - McLean Art Center - Molly Vick, 1988; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Najawa Dance Corps., 1980-1987; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter, 1980-1984; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Articles about The REP, Inc. (1/3), 1972-1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles about The REP, Inc. (2/3), 1972-1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles about The REP, Inc. (3/3), 1972-1988; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles - Mounted, 1975; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Office Administration - Bills and Receipts, 1979-1986; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Office Administration - Bulletin Board Morgue, 1984; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Office Administration - Contract Form: Four Use of Rep. Space, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Office of Administration - Inter-Office Meeting Notes (Ayo's 1984), Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Office Policies and Procedures: (Work-Up File), 1984; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Office Administration - Organizational and Legal Documents, 1984; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - General and from "Imani", c. 1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Evaluation, 1981-1983; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Planning and Evaluation - Amendments: Articles of Inc., 1981-1983; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Planning and Evaluation - Bylaws (Predates 1983), n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Production Technical Records, 1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Publicity - Press Releases, 1980-1985; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Publicity - Flyers (1/2), 1972-1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Publicity - Flyers (2/2), 1972-1992; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Publicity - Programs (1/2), 1972-1992; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Publicity - Programs (2/2), 1972-1992; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Reinstatement Documents, 1973; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Resource Development, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Resumes and Biographies, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reviews, 1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Script - "Five on the Backhand Side", 1979; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Script - "Miss Ann Don't Cry No More", 1976; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Script - "Oh Oh Freedom", 1975; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Tax Exempt Certificate Status, 1978-1983; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tax Form 990, 1980-1982; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Technical/Artistic Personnel Interviews: Appointment Book, 1984; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tenth Anniversary Reception, 1982; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Timesheets, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Touring Package, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Volunteers, n.d., undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Theatre material, 1971-2000; Series 3
  This series includes material related to the theatre, including scripts, poetry, resumes of actors and technicians, as well as items related to theatre maintenance and equipment. Dates covered include 1971-2000.
  - Budgets, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - How to Extract a Mono from a Play for Filing Mono File, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - How to Write a Play Synopsis, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Job Descriptions, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Macbeth - Budget Spreadsheet and Purchase Orders, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Measurement Chart/Female, ca. 1980s; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mono and Synopsis File: General Correspondence, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Overtime Costs, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Management Training, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Petty Cash, 1978-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Poetry - The Book of Negroe Folklore, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Poetry - I Am the River Niger, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Poetry - The Jabberwocky, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Poetry - Miscellaneous File, 1999; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Poetry - J.A. Johnson, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Poetry - Now the Way of the Mecca Was on the Wise, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Poetry - Steal Away, Steal Away, Steal Away Home..., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Poetry - The World of Gwendolyn Brooks, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Publications, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Purchase Orders, Checks, 1986-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Rental Deposits, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Rental Deposit Refunds, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Resume - Alexander, Dimitri, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Resume - Blomberg, Elody R., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Resume - Brown, Helen Xiney: Designer, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Resume - Byrnes, James C., 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Resume - Calloway, Fredella, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Resume - Catesby, Jameson, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Resume - Council, Linda, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Resume - Golbert, Reggie, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Resume - Dobkin, Avrom, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Resume - Goldberg, Michael, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Resume - Guy, Joyce M., 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Resume - Habberton, John, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Resume - Hackland, Norman, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Resume - Halko, Michel, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Resume - Hall, Jo-Ann, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Resume - Herring, Ben L., 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Resume - Hill-Davis, Gloria, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Resume - Howze, Tyrone, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Resume - Jensen, John Christian, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Resume - Kollmorgen, Steve, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Resume - Kostin, Kathryn: Light Design, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Resume - Krentzlin, Doug, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Resume - Larr Avide, Jack, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Resume - Lerer, Larry, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Resume - Manago, Toni, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Resume - Mark, Charles C., 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Resume - Mayfield, Brenda F., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Resume - Metcalf, Reginald, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Resume - Michael, James, 1984; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Resume - Miscellaneous: Last Names A-C, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Resume - Miscellaneous: Last Names D-I, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Resume - Miscellaneous: Last Names J-M, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Resume - Miscellaneous: Last Names N-S, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Resume - Miscellaneous: Last Name T-Z, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Resume - Morris-Tebang, Nakita, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Resume - Mountain, Christa, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Resume - Parisi, Jim, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Resume - Pettus, William, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Resume - Pettus, William Jr., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Resume - Porter, Kelly, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Resume - Robelen, Elizabeth, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Resume - Rogas, Linda C., 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Resume - Rosenberg, Carol, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Resume - Ross, Brian J., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Resume - San Martino, Rose Ann, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Resume - Savard, Manette, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Resume - Sawyer, Gail, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Resume - Schmoll, Joanne, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Resume - Silverman, Julie, 1984; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Resume - Stage Notes, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Resume - Status Sheets, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Resume - Status Sheets, 1984; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Resume - Thomas, Teresa (Tabia), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Resume - Taylor, Billie, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Resume - Wagner, Kimberly, 1976; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Resume - Walker, Deborah A., n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Resume - Wallace, Rodney A., 1984; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Script - After Hours, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Script - The Amen Corner, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Script - Banquet in Honor of Langston Hughes, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Script - Birdbath, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Script - Black Jesus, 1972; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Script - Black Masks, 1986; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Script - Breakfast in Harlem (1/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Script - Breakfast in Harlem (2/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Script - The Breakout, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Script - Brownstone, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Script - Character Study, 1973-1978; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Script - Dark at the Top of the Stairs, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Script - Daybreak Dreams, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Script - Deen Down in the Jungle, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Script - Don't Bother Me, I Can't Cope, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Script - Don't Leave Go My Hand, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Script - East of Jordan, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)